<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-22T10:30:29-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">NotAnExpert</title><subtitle>The thoughs and experiences of a constant beginer. I am not an expert. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Home Automation: Mission Statement</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/homeautomation/hass/ha/2020/05/21/HomeAutomation-mission-statement.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Home Automation: Mission Statement" /><published>2020-05-21T13:00:32-04:00</published><updated>2020-05-21T13:00:32-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/homeautomation/hass/ha/2020/05/21/HomeAutomation-mission-statement</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/homeautomation/hass/ha/2020/05/21/HomeAutomation-mission-statement.html">&lt;p&gt;I have had the dream of Home Automation for years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all of the time I have developed my own personal mission statement. The mission statement boils down to the mindset I use when implementing new devices in services to further the dream of a fully automated home. My goals and mission boils down to two words:
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;just-work&quot;&gt;&lt;center&gt;JUST WORK!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t mind tinkering around making different peices fit together to solve a problem. And If I end up breaking something that is my fault and I will take lumps. BUT I need to trust that when my wife or kids hit a button that installed, it has to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;cloud-connected-services&quot;&gt;Cloud Connected Services&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All around the home automation communities a common theme is often hate and mistrust about services that require access to back-end resources hosted in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;protocols&quot;&gt;Protocol(s)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Z-Wave / ZigBee / Wifi / ETC all begin on equal footing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I have had the dream of Home Automation for years. In all of the time I have developed my own personal mission statement. The mission statement boils down to the mindset I use when implementing new devices in services to further the dream of a fully automated home. My goals and mission boils down to two words: JUST WORK! I don’t mind tinkering around making different peices fit together to solve a problem. And If I end up breaking something that is my fault and I will take lumps. BUT I need to trust that when my wife or kids hit a button that installed, it has to work. Cloud Connected Services All around the home automation communities a common theme is often hate and mistrust about services that require access to back-end resources hosted in the cloud. Protocol(s) Z-Wave / ZigBee / Wifi / ETC all begin on equal footing.</summary></entry></feed>